Transcription by ESO. Translation by —
And now I'm leaving.
コトリのように目覚めた日を見たいなんて当たり前に来るものだと思っていた
Thank you.
You do what you have to do, too.
And besides, what other choice do you have?
You're another me.
It's there.
One of your feathers.
No, forget about the feathers.
Don't do this.
I will recover your feathers.
I swear on my life.
Don't run!
Summon all wins!
You are only an incarnation of me.
One of us has to die.
I wonder if Charon's all right.
Unfortunately, I cannot enter into dreams anymore.
All I can do is believe in him and hope that he'll return to us again soon.
Malkina believes in him.
Aren't you going to?
I don't have the power to do that anymore, but regardless, even if I had my magic, I'd wait here, although it's hard.
I got into hot water.
I got into hot water there.
I'd have to disagree.
I think you put him in hot water.
If I didn't know better, I'd think you intended to hand over the feather from the beginning.
You're getting soft.
Maybe.
What am I going to do with you?
You can't help baiting everyone you like.
That's why those twins are running away from you, you know.
It wasn't easy, having Kamui hate me the way he did.
You got what was coming to you.
Oh?
Not still.
I can't help hoping they're able to make a safe return.
It might be harder than it seems, though.
It might be harder than me,
if you don't know.
Or if he's a large volume downer I guess I'm
gonna dive honestly or think about.
You're there ever more than you looking
should've been aif.
Don't fear.
Oh!
Um...
Uh...
Soade.
What will your team keep doing one last rig,
Let's go.
Back away.
All I require is the princesses' body.
You can have her soul.
It really makes no difference to me.
Go on. Get out of the way.
Memories of the body.
Even though the mind has forgotten, sometimes the body will still remember.
How annoying. In that case, we'll have to start with the original Shaoran.
I promised you. I'd find your feathers.
And no one will stand in my way.
No!
You can't do this!
If you kill your other self, all of this will end!
Please, you'll end this too, Shaoran!
Kill him now.
Goodbye!
It's the kid.
No, Shaoran.
Can you tell what's going on inside the barrier?
Yes.
Oh, my God.
Sakura!
Oi!
What is this?
Sharon!
Sakura!
I'm not who you think I am. I'm not your Sakura.
Hey, who are you?
You know?
I wonder if we were always meant to meet each other.
Guess what? It's almost time for my birthday.
About what I mentioned a minute ago.
That thing I need to say to you?
I'll tell you next time, okay?
Don't you see it yet?
Don't you realize how alike we are?
But you knew that already, didn't you?
This whole time you were aware that I wasn't the real Sakura.
It wasn't my soul that loved Princess Sakura.
That part of it was yours, wasn't it?
I'm sorry.
And...
Thank you, Shao.
Your Sakura's waiting.
She's there.
And so, please, from now on, for the sake of the one you truly hold dear, be free.
You and I are both artificial creations.
They are the same.
Do you see now?
As long as those two keep living, it isn't over.
I love you, Shao.
I...
No!
It's Dr. Kyle.
He was in Jade Country and Piffle World, too.
Put the soccer up.
Where is she going?
Now I will be taking this with me.
No, he won't!
No, wait!
Come back!
Saron!
Please get up!
Sakura is gone!
He took Sakura with him!
The other Saron's disappeared, too.
Sakura's soul! Is it gone?
Sakura's soul!
Is it gone?
Did the princess know all this time? And did she know she was a clone, too?
Sakura probably realized all this after she got her feather back in Tokyo?
She was never the same after that. She changed.
And it wasn't just because the other Saron had vanished.
It wasn't that she couldn't accept who you were, Saron.
It wasn't that she couldn't accept who you were, Saron. That's not it at all.
She realized that she was also a clone.
And it wasn't just because the other Saron had vanished.
It wasn't that she couldn't accept who you were, Saron. That's not it at all.
She realized that she was also a clone.
She knew then that your real Sakura was someone else entirely.
She kept herself distant on purpose.
From now on,
it was the same.
She was the same after that.
She changed.
And it wasn't just because the other Saron had vanished.
It wasn't that she couldn't accept who you were, Saron.
That's not it at all.
She realized that she was also a clone.
She knew then that your real Sakura was someone else entirely.
She kept herself distant on purpose.
From now on,
from now on,
be free.
Perhaps she knew,
but even so,
she always did whatever she could
to shape the dream in which she lived.
Tell me, how long have you known about this?
From the beginning.
From the person
who set up this journey.
So I did my best.
To grant any wish in my power.
Whenever I was able to.
I was able to.
The difference is his clone was nothing more than a duplication of the original Saron.
And that Saron placed his soul inside the clone.
Sakura is different.
Both her body and soul were duplicated.
And so, the feathers that were scattered were the same as those produced by the original Sakura.
But why would her clone be made differently from the kids?
Maybe.
The clone was disposable.
It could die.
But as long as there was still the original.
Fei Wang could easily have swapped her out.
Or so he thought.
He would repeat the process as often as it was necessary.
Even if doing so meant that a life would be ended.
Artificial or not, he would gladly sacrifice her.
So then, what about her soul?
Is it gone too?
Sakura!
Ooh!
Even if she was fake, she was my friend!
And now she's gone!
Yes, you're right.
I've always been watching her.
I've seen her journey.
And that's why...
I will get her back.
Anyone would have the same dream as Fei Wang.
If they had lost someone important to them.
But still, someone who is lost cannot ever be returned.
What about Sakura's body?
Where do you think it's been taken?
Mekyo?
I have a wish, Yuko.
I need to find Sakura.
Can you tell me where she is?
Which Sakura are you looking for?
Both of them.
No matter what happens, I won't let her die.
And if I give him this information, what do you other two intend to do about it?
Join him.
Absolutely.
You know, Yuko?
This reminds me of when they first came to the shop.
About the price.
It has already been paid for me.
What?
Who paid?
He's closer to Shaoram than anyone.
He's someone who once paid me the same compensation as the princess.
The one who was traveling with you.
The same price as Sakura, but that means...
With memories.
Yes, that's it exactly.
He has forgotten his past and the names of his parents, and even that he has already paid this price.
He has forgotten it all.
What's your name?
I'm Watanuki Kamihiro.
Watanuki?
That means April 1st, doesn't it?
Wait, how could you possibly have known that?
I've asked you about it before.
Although I imagine you don't remember it.
It was for the same wish you're making now, Shaoram.
You're seeking Fei Wang Reed.
He's in Cloud Country.
In a time that's detached from reality.
I have obtained this body and the dimensions engraved upon it by reading time and places, as well as manipulating the lives of others.
At last, it's finally in my power. Without it, all my efforts would have come to naught.
So then where is the original Sakura's body?
After I created this clone body, the other died.
Of course I had foreseen that eventuality. All I need is the body I have right here.
Along with the princess's soul, I'll have the power to transcend space and time and grant my wish.
Your older brother seems to be quite busy.
Even after your kind invitation, he insisted he needed to get to the next world.
The others, though, they're the ones who should really be in a hurry.
Your brother appeared to have a wish of his own, as well.
Yes. And he will sacrifice anything to make it come true.
All happiness and unhappiness is very much alike.
They are both rooted in our desires.
Which is why people will forever continue to wish.
I hope Mokono will be able to get a little sleep tonight.
Sakura...
Come in.
I didn't even knock and you already knew I was there.
You always have.
No matter where I hit trying to surprise you.
You would always find me right away, Kurogane. Always.
It's a small part of what it means to be a warrior.
No matter where someone is hiding, I can find them.
Especially if it's you.
This is Ginryo.
I'm sorry, Kurogane. I've had it with me all this time. I chose to hold onto it instead of bearing it with your mother.
I had to, though, for that was her last wish. She called me to Sua. I spoke with her before she died.
Tsumoyo.
Yes?
Once again, I'm going to be leaving Japan for a time. But I will return shortly without fail. So I swear to you again.
All that I am is for my master. And all that I am belongs only to her. I swear this is the greatest truth I've known in my life. I swear on my true name known only to my master.
Then good hunting, dear Yuo.
I hope I'm not disturbing you.
I want to thank you. For Sakura. For staying by her side this whole time. I only wish I could have done more.
You were there for her, and that's what matters most. We should look for her. She's out there.
Yes.
Kurogane and Sai are in their original clothes.
And those clothes? I've been saving them for Shara.
Mokona? Yes, Yuko?
You will have only one chance to get into Cloud Country.
Watanuki gave up his memories to find Beowong Reed's location and give you this opportunity. So do everything that you can.
Thank you.
We know how you treasure the princess. We wish you good luck in bringing her back.
Let's go. To Cloud Country.
Welcome to Cloud Country.
cockpiguen.
I'll see you next time.